Hurry up.
Gong Xi,
you don't have to be so exaggerated.
My son-in-law,
if My Lord knows that
I meet you privately behind her back,
I will be kicked out.
I asked you out today
just to ask
why your article
ended so early?
You two aren't together,
I have nothing to write about,
so I have to stop writing.
That's a shame.
Princess Langyue
is still waiting for the sequel.
Really?
My son-in-law,
you should find a way to get back to the Escort Agency.
Come with me.
Okay.
This is my plan.
Grandfather has received my rent.
At least he won't oppose me.
Uncle
is originally my enemy.
It's hard to deal with him.
I don't know about brother.
But he will oppose me with Tang Xin.
I'll contact with Jiaojiao.
As for you,
I don't worry about you.
But
I have to
leave Fa Cai to you.
My son-in-law,
you want to
defeat them one by one?
Uncle,
the best Yunzhonghe.
The dishes are ready. Enjoy yourself.
Here.
Uncle.
What do you want to do?
You didn't poison me, did you?
Uncle
My wish now
is to go back to the Escort Agency.
Su Yuejiao doesn't want you.
Even if I eat and drink a lot,
I can't help it.
As long as you don't object.
Then
I'll invite you to drink and eat every month.
Am I that easy to please?
At least every half month.
Come on.
Come on, uncle.
Cheers, uncle.
Just do this.
Do you understand?
Go, go.
Okay, okay.
Look at the Su's Escort Agency.
Now they don't even use carriages to escort.
No wonder there are so few escorts.
Yeah.
I heard that Mr. Cheng reads novels during the day
and writes chapters all night.
It's all for the business of the agency.
Really?
Mr. Cheng is really working hard.
Without him,
Su's Escort Agency would have closed long ago.
Yeah.
Xin,
give it to me.
the earrings
look great on you.
How are Cheng Qi and Jiaojiao doing?
It seems that
Cheng Qi has already won over Uncle and Facha.
Next,
it's likely to be you and me.
You should be wary of Cheng Qi's honeyed words.
I only care about Jiaojiao's choice.
But you,
don't be blinded by Cheng Qi.
Don't worry.
Qi.
Qi is a sister and wife slave.
With Jiaojiao's attitude now,
and Tang Xin's complaints about you,
he won't let you go back.
How about starting with Tang Xin?
But he also listens to his grandfather.
I think we should go straight to Daqi.
Besides Tang Xin,
what else can't he resist?
Wood.
Thank you all.
I have a plan.
Sir, this way.
Sir,
this wood...
You have a good eye.
This is the best rosewood in our shop.
The color is light,
the texture is loose,
exquisite and beautiful.
The utensils made of
rosewood in our shop
are all covered with a very beautiful texture.
I know it very well.
How much?
It's not for sale.
This one is made of Qinglong wood, which is unique to Langyue.
The wood is very hard,
suitable for carving various handicrafts.
The wooden ware made of Qinglong wood
has a beautiful
satin-like gloss.
How much is this one?
It's not for sale.
If you don't sell any of them,
why are you introducing them to me?
It's for you.
For free?
Why?
Because you are a man of justice,
and know how to save others from the water and fire.
And you, sir,
you don't hold grudges,
and know how to make a marriage.
You...
Brother
I was wrong.
I'll never say anything that makes her unhappy.
Please give me another chance.
Let me back to the Escort Agency, okay?
I'll be nice to her in the future.
Brother
Calm down.
People would think
I bullied you if they see you like this.
Brother, I beg you.
Please let me back to the Agency.
Even if I go out earlier,
and take more escorts,
I'll have more time to accompany Jiao.
Aren't you afraid of her beating you?
It's good for her to beat me.
It proves that I still have a chance.
Brother
I swear that
from now on, if you have any confusion about love,
I'll give you free consulting.
It's not that I don't want to help you.
As long as you don't object,
I'll have my way.
I can turn a blind eye.
But
if I hurt the Escort Agency again,
I'll be damned.
But
if I fail to cherish Jia again,
I'll die in a bad way.
You...you...you let me go first.
No, brother.
Let go of me.
But I can't carry
so much wood back by myself.
Why are you here?
Jiao.
Sit down.
This little book stall has been so popular lately.
And our neighbors are very enthusiastic.
I suggest we open two more sessions, morning and evening.
This way, it won't interfere with your schedule,
and can also attract more customers.
You're not answering my question.
I'm asking you,
why are you on my dinner table?
Jiaojiao,
how can you talk to the guest like this?
Guest?
He wants to open two sessions a day,
how tired the back and forth journey is.
So,
I rent this guest room.
No way.
As the head of the Su's Escort Agency,
I ask you to leave.
You will get your rent back.
I've been having bad luck
playing cards recently.
Mr. Wang next door has won all my pocket money
in the past few months.
Shi,
take the money to your uncle later.
Gong Xi,
Have I paid off my debt to Huayue Tower?
Qi,
the escort vehicles and boxes are worn out.
They need to be repaired before use.
Grandpa,
I have many new inventions recently.
But I have no money to buy materials.
Well,
I don't think you collect rent,
but drug.
Eat up.
Dad.
Eat.
Come on.
I don't drink.
I can't sleep.
I want to go back to the Moon God Pavilion.
I have a question for you.
Between me and Meng Feifei, who do you choose?
Between me and Mr. Su, who do you choose?
I choose you.
Come back.
Where are you going?
Back to the Moon God Pavilion.
This agency can't hold me.
Look at you.
You can't stand a day without Meng Feifei.
My Lord.
Take a look at yourself first.
Everyone's here.
Eat.
I'm exhausted.
Jiao.
Here.
Will we have hot breakfast
after morning exercises?
Yes.
Jiao will have it.
What do you mean?
Others may not have it.
Burn the bridge
after crossing it.
Jiao.
I know you can't take care of it.
You take this food box.
I...
I'm sorry.
What are they looking at?
My Lord,
the story the young man is telling
is about a young man who spent a fortune
on books to help a scholar pass the exam.
My Lady,
you've just been released from confinement.
If the master and the young master know it,
who is so stupid
to make up stories?
It seems that we can't hear the new chapter today.
Go, go.
Cheng Qi,
you could have gone further.
It doesn't matter.
As long as I can tell my stories,
it's enough.
Today's performance is over.
Please come back
early tomorrow.
The official performance
is being prepared.
I can help you get a chance to perform.
Thank you for your kindness.
I'm sorry
to let you come all this way.
Cheng Qi,
who do you think you are?
How dare you be so ungrateful?
I'm just a nobody,
letting you down.
Now,
this script
is the most important thing to me.
This is the important thing?
The top student of Xingyun Academy performing on the street
is just to help Su Yuejiao protect the escort agency?
What's wrong with performing on the street?
Good words are wonderful everywhere.
In your eyes,
she's just a bodyguard.
But in my eyes,
she's my family for life.
Miss Zhang,
I'm no longer the leader of the Xingyun.
I hope you
won't make it hard for the escort agency and Jia anymore.
Okay.
Remember what you said today.
What a tenant you are!
You delayed the dinner of the whole family.
Hurry up.
You've been talking for so long. Aren't you hungry?
Okay.
Give it to me.
Yummy, yummy.
Gong Xi, Fa Cai. [*Happy Chinese New Year.]
Here.
Let me see.
See it later.
The boss will notice it.
See it later, got it?
What are you hiding?
The top and the little escort.
Face and the little escort.
Life and the little escort.
The scholar's answer
has always been the little escort.
Someone wants to use the scholar.
He started the contest
and framed the escort
to threaten the scholar.
The scholar was eager to save people,
so he fell into the trap.
He thought that he could stop the danger
by pushing the escort away.
But in the end,
both of them were hurt.
I told you to go back to the room,
but you didn't listen.
Now the boss is angry.
What kind of mediocrity did Zhang Qijia find?
It seems that they are all recommended by Mr. Ling.
The works of the noble family
are mediocre in rhetoric
and hollow in content.
They want to attend the speech meeting of the official.
One Ling Feng is not enough,
and they find these people to make up the number.
I think,
the meeting will eventually
return to Cheng Qi.
But didn't Cheng Qi
start storytelling on the street?
Will the official really use him?
He just chooses to be a commoner,
not lack of talent.
He still has the potential to rise.
This time,
the first phase of the plan
of the plan is successful.
What should we do in the second stage?
Propose.
Isn't that the final stage?
Tomorrow?
Isn't it too risky?
How about discussing it with Feifei?
It was because of my hesitation before
that led to all sorts of misunderstandings.
This time,
I'll be proactive and direct.
If I fail,
I'll try again.
He said in front of everyone
that you are his family.
Wait.
Cheng Qi moved into the agency.
Su Yuqi didn't tell me.
And you didn't tell me either.
Do you even consider me family?
I didn't let him move in.
Then what's his scheme this time?
You should have kicked him out.
Xin,
I think
you're right.
What did I say?
The best way to forget someone
is to find a new person to replace him.
You finally figured it out.
Wait.
Did Cheng Qi
do something wrong to you?
No.
Then you met someone better than him.
No, no.
That's impossible.
Tell me what's going on now,
or we'll break up.
I'm afraid that
I'll go back to him.
No, no.
Stop in time.
It's never too late to turn back.
Tell me,
what kind of person are you looking for this time?
I'll turn the whole city upside down
to find a way for you.
No need.
I already have a suitable candidate.
Is it another extraordinary person
you met during your escort missions?
How's that?
Son-in-law,
you'll do.
If you're too nervous to speak later,
just read this.
Don't be afraid.
She can't eat you.
Since everyone is here,
I have something to announce.
I've been in charge for a while.
I was too willful before
and put the Escort Agency in danger.
It was my fault.
Now the Agency is back on track.
It's time for me
to find a helper
for myself and the Escort Agency.
So moving.
Where's my pen?
I don't have to read the book secretly.
You finally forgive me.
Jiao.
My sister-in-law.
Wait for me.
Let me introduce him to you.
This is Da Bao,
the son of Zhen Yuwai.
He's good at martial arts and well-behaved.
He's a rare talent.
Since he's the good match chosen by my uncle,
and everyone knows him,
I decide to
get along with him.
Nonsense!
They are just swindlers who took money.
Well,
Since no one has any objections,
we'll choose a day for the marriage.
You!
Dad,
I really had nothing to do with this.
Bao,
who bought you candy?
It's my sister.
Bao,
is it sweet?
Yes, as sweet as my sister.
My Lord, did you eat something wrong?
Or are you drunk?
Gao Jiao
I don't believe you really want to marry him.
Since I have taken over the position,
I must take responsibility for the Escort Agency.
It's my mother's tradition to find a husband to escort.
Dabao's Kung Fu is so cute.
And he's obedient.
What's wrong with him?
I'm cute, too.
I can also obey you.
How about this?
Let me compete with him.
If I win,
you let him go,
and I'll marry you.
No way.
I think it's okay.
Jiaojiao,
you may have forgotten.
When Dabao wanted to marry into the family,
he proposed a duel with Cheng Qi.
We agreed.
Now Cheng Qi wants to duel with Dabao.
We should also...
Then let them duel.
Okay.
Jiaojiao,
Cheng Qi knows no martial arts.
If they duel,
he's bound to lose.
I was late last time.
This time,
I'll win him fairly.
Jiaojiao,
I'm determined
to marry you.
What are you thinking?
Compete with Zhen Dabao?
Yeah, my son-in-law.
Even I'm afraid of his fists.
If you can withstand a punch, you're lucky.
I think you'd better give up.
Jiaojiao may not really want to marry him.
Maybe she just wants to make you mad,
and give up.
I don't care.
My grandpa set the date for five days later.
I must find a way to beat him in these five days.
Why don't you listen to me?
What can you do in five days?
Let Daqi make you a suit of armor.
You just go to be beaten.
You'll be so heavy that you can't run.
Stand there and take a beating?
I think
you'd better buy some candies.
Use candies as weapons.
Time waits for no man.
Why don't you
teach him kung fu first
and think about
winning by ingenuity?
That's all we can do.
We can't let Jiaojiao make trouble.
Uncle,
I'll leave escorting to you these days.
Start special training tomorrow.
My back!
This is as fast and strong as I can get.
At least it's an improvement.
Today's special training
is the most important part.
getting hit.
Remember,
don't move later.
Feel the force,
neutralize it,
and wear down your opponent's strength
and patience.
Learn to rely on protection to dissipate force.
Only then will you have the chance to wear down the opponent.
To feel the force,
and to resolve the force.
It's just a story to fool girls.
It's not that exaggerated.
You don't understand.
Other stories are made up.
His is different.
He made it up.
What?
Watching you training in the training ground,
my heart was stirred.
He never got up.
That was before.
Now it's different.
It's a pity that there's only half a book.
I don't know what he wrote later.
Will he write me in?
Which is more important, this book
or Yikeba's movements?
You've been in his camp for so long.
You just drink every day.
He won't take you out for about another half month.
Yesterday, when drinking,
a general didn't show up.
The one who patrols the border?
No.
The one in charge of supplies.
That's strange.
There's no relocation plan,
and it's not time for a supply run.
But he's going out for several days.
He must be transporting something.
I sent the men Jalur found for me
to tail him.
You have to find a reason
to let me leave the barracks for a few days.
It's easy.
Just say I want you to accompany me for a few days.
Learn from these scripts to deceive young girls.
Change one.
I like this one.
I...
What are you doing at the door?
I'm waiting for you
to come.
It's made to your size.
It can save your life in case of emergency.
Be careful when you put it on.
I know.
Thank you for helping me.
Pay attention tomorrow.
Act according to the situation.
Don't be careless.
Don't worry.
The only matrilocal husband of Su's Escort Agency
can only be me.
He's quite proud.
Mom,
is he stupid?
He knows he can't win,
yet he still agreed to the duel.
Does he have to stay at the agency?
Mom,
you don't care about me anymore?
Jiaojiao.
Grandpa, why are you here?
Actually, I'm here every time
you come to see your mother.
I also miss your grandma.
Then you
heard it all.
What?
Can't I listen?
No.
Jiaojiao,
you are the only girl in the family.
When you grow up, some things are not convenient to say.
It's okay not to say.
But I have a word
for you about him.
He left the Escort Agency and hurt you.
Although he didn't say it,
there must be a reason.
Grandpa
can guess it.
I know
him well.
He loves you
and the Escort Agency.
If the Cheng Qi in your heart
is the same as the one I see,
why not give him another chance?
But Grandpa,
he will definitely lose
in tomorrow's martial arts contest.
Love is hard to win,
but also hard to lose.
You'll know
soon enough.